本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版
嘿  泰迪熊宝宝
Hey, Teddy bear.
别这么叫我
Don't call me that.
-PJ  -其实我想问你个问题
-P.J. -Actually I had a question for you.
关于我的燕尾服
For my tuxedo, should I go.
应该选橘色还是藏蓝
With tangerine or powder blue?
PJ
P.J.
租豪华礼车似乎有点贵
And the limo was kind of expensive,
所以我爷爷准备开旅行车载咱俩去
So my grandpa is gonna drive us in his station wagon.
好了  我知道我问你后一定会后悔的
Okay, I'm gonna regret asking this,
但是你在说什么呢
But what are you talking about?
返校舞会啊  你是我的舞伴
Homecoming dance. You're my date.
再问你一遍  你说啥呢
Again, what are you talking about?
你答应过我  要和我一起去的
You promised you'd go with me.
埃米特  醒醒
Emmett, wake up.
我没做梦  你看
I'm not dreaming, okay?
2004年4月19日
April 19, 2004...
你答应我要和我一起参加返校舞会
You agreed to go to homecoming dance with me.
-我有证据  -那好  拿来看看
-I have proof. -Well, let's see the proof.
好的
Okay.
嘿  泰迪熊宝宝
Hey, Teddy bear.
别这么叫我
Don't call me that.
能做我的女朋友吗
Will you be my girlfriend?
不
No.
现在呢
How about now?
不
No.
好吧  不如这样
Okay, how about this?
如果高中我还交不到女朋友
If I don't have a girlfriend in High School,
那你愿意和我一起参加返校舞会吗
Will you go to the homecoming dance with me?
如果我同意了  你能从我眼前消失吗
If I say yes, will you get out of my face?
-好的  -那我答应了
-Yes. -Then yes.
好耶  都拍下来了吗  PJ
Yes! You got that, pj?
埃米特  那时候我们都还小
Emmett, we were just kids.
你不会认真了吧  对吧
You're not gonna actually make me go, are you?
我爷爷不喜欢夜间开车
My grandpa doesn't like to drive at night,
所以请在四点半左右准备好
So be ready around 4:30.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast </i>
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late, and dad jokes</i>
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>Has anybody seen my left shoe</i>
■
翻译： Johnny-Z
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite</i>
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud</i>
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof</i>
■
校订： line
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I've survived</i>
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice</i>
■
后期： Johnny-Z  liloelva
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy</i>
可是我知道你会有美好将来
<i>But I know your future's bright</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
不要怀疑
<i>There's no maybe</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Your life is up and down</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me it comes back around</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love</i> <i>who you turn out to be</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第二季第二十二集
Good Luck Charlie  S02E22  The Bob Duncan Experience
噢  嘿
Oh hey.
你猜我在车库找到了什么
Guess what I just found in the garage.
噢  又没有好事
Ooh, those are never good words.
请允许我介绍下我的高中乐队
May I introduce my High School band:
鲍伯·邓肯体验乐队
The Bob Duncan experience?
哈哈  看看
Ha ha. Look at that.
这是里奇  这是马蒂
There's Richie. There's Marty.
中间这个帅哥就是你老爸我
And check out your old man in the middle there, huh?
像我吧
That look familiar?
呃  不像
Um... No.
噢  拜托了  PJ  我长得多像你
Oh, come on, P.J., I look just like you.
我没看出来
I don't see it.
咱们就是一对双胞胎
We could be twins.
我看还是算了吧
I choose not to see it.
好吧  我们录了一张专辑
All right. We made an album.
快瞧瞧  多给力
Check that out. Pretty rad, huh?
是啊  鲍伯·邓肯
Right, "the Bob Duncan..."
-体验乐队  -不  不
-"experience." -No no!
噢  天啊  该死
Oh! Aw man! Oh shoot!
呃  能用胶水或者胶带粘好吗
Uh, can we... can we glue it or tape it or...
算了  算了  已经坏了
No no, it's gone.
这不会是绝版吧
That... that wasn't the only one, right?
绝版了  我告诉过你  我们录了一张专辑
Yeah. Well, I told you, we made<i>an</i> album.
老爸  太抱歉了
Dad, I am so sorry.
算了  没事的
No, it's all right.
都是我的错  不该有些美好的回忆
It's my fault for having sweet memories...
和孩子
And kids.
好了  海盗查莉  让我看下伤口
Okay, pirate Charlie, let me see your boo-boo.
真不应该让你两只眼睛上都戴眼罩
Not a good idea to wear a patch on both eyes.
嗨  小伙子们  柠檬汁卖得怎么样啊
Hi, guys. How's the lemonade business?
太好了  多亏了利奥独家柠檬汁秘方
Great, thanks to Leo's awesome lemonade recipe.
噢  也不全是我的功劳
Oh, I can't take all the credit.
你是想到要去偷
It was your idea to steal...
我是说向达布尼太太的柠檬树上借些柠檬
I mean borrow the lemons from Mrs. Dabney's tree.
盖比  你从达布尼太太那里偷柠檬
Gabe, you stole lemons from Mrs. Dabney?
我希望这不会引来杀身之祸
I hope this doesn't come back to bite me in the...
您好  达布尼太太
Hello, Mrs. Dabney.
柠檬吗
Lemons?
我什么事也不知道
I don't know anything about lemons.
-明天我们还要这么做  -绝对
-We should do this again tomorrow. -Definitely.
-分一下钱吧  -好的
-Hey, let's divide up the profits. -Yeah.
好的  我们赚了
Okay, so we made...
大约是四十块二十五美分
Looks like $40.25.
-给你  -酷
-So here. -Cool.
为什么你拿走那二十五美分
Why do you get the quarter?
我以为是平均分钱
I thought we were partners.
好吧  那再把这二十五美分平摊
Fine, we'll split the quarter.
十二美分吗
12 cents?
为什么你多拿一美分
Why do you get the extra Penny?
因为是我出的好点子
Because it was my idea.
我就是这组织的大脑
I'm the brains of this operation.
没错  但我起码也是花瓶啊
Yeah, but I'm the eye candy.
好了  别吵了
Okay, this is stupid.
如果下次再有多余的一美分  你拿走
The next time we have an extra Penny, you can have it.
-我想要这次的  -这次是我的
-I want this one. -This one's mine.
-你在犯浑  -你在犯大浑
-You're being a jerk. -You're being a... Jerky jerk.
你居然自称大脑
And you call yourself the brains.
告诉你吧  留好你那一美分
You know what? Keep your precious Penny.
这个组合解散了
This partnership is over.
随便  我不需要你
Fine. I don't need you.
我也不需要你  我谁都不需要
I don't need you. I don't need anybody.
我需要你妈  她要送我回家
I need your mom. She's my ride.
噢  嘿  艾米特  艾米特  和你说点事
Oh hey, Emmett, Emmett. Uh, we need to talk.
好的  我的舞伴  她是我的舞伴
Sure thing, homecoming date. She's my homecoming date!
话别说早了
Maybe not.
这边来  来坐下
Here we go. Let's just sit.
在那个视频里  你说的是
So in that video your exact words were
如果你没有女朋友
I had to go to homecoming with you.
我就陪你去返校舞会
Unless you had a girlfriend.
-所以呢  -所以我给你找了个女朋友
-So? -So I'm gonna get you one.
噢  太搞笑了
Oh, that's funny.
别笑  别笑  我是认真的
No no, I'm serious.
有个新来的女生
There's this new girl in school
我觉着你俩挺般配
and I think she's perfect for you.
怎么个般配
What makes her perfect?
她完全没听说过你
She doesn't know anything about you.
她叫艾丽西娅
So her name is Alicia.
她很可爱  很有魅力
She's very sweet. She is very attractive.
所以我要想办法让你看起来
So I just have to figure out a way to make you...
很诱人
Appealing.
做起来容易吗  不容易
Is it gonna be easy? No.
能成功吗
Is it gonna be doable?
只许成功  不许失败
It has to be.
嘿  老爸  过来下  给你个惊喜
Hey, dad! Come up here. I got a surprise.
一听就没好事
Those are never good words.
-里奇  -鲍比
-Richie! -Bobby!
看看你  一点也没变
Look at you! You haven't changed at all!
哈  再看看你
Ha, and you...
啊  鲍比
Ah, Bobby!
-你  你怎么来了  -PJ打电话给我了
-What... what are you doing here? -P.J. Called me up.
听说乐队要重出江湖
Something about getting the band back together.
老爸  我真的很抱歉弄坏了你的专辑
Dad, I felt so bad about breaking the album,
我想你们这帮家伙可以再录一张
I thought you guys could make another one.
PJ  这想法太好了
P.J., this is fantastic.
嘿  你联系到疯子马蒂了吗
Hey, did you track down madman Marty?
联系到了  但他来不了了  他参加读书会了
Yeah yeah. He can't make it... book club.
但他依旧很疯狂  只不过现在对书而疯狂
No, he's still a madman, just with books.
对了  PJ可以当吉他手
Well, hey, P.J. Can sit in on guitar.
太好了
This is great!
鲍伯·邓肯体验乐队回归了
The Bob Duncan experience is back!
这动作什么时候结束
How... how long do we do this?
直到脑海里的欢呼声逐渐消失
Until the imaginary applause dies down.
挺冷清的啊
Kind of quiet around here.
想知道为什么吗
Want to know why?
“利奥的柠檬汁小筑”  你在和我竞争
"Leo's lemonade lounge"? You're competing with me?
竞争意味着要比赛
Competing would imply competition.
从现在看来  连个竞争对手都没有
And from what I see, hmph, I don't have any.
“利奥的”里面的“的”字写反了
The "s" in "leo's" is backwards.
我故意的  这样看起来可爱
I did that on purpose. It's cuter.
难道“檬”字有两个木字旁  也是为了可爱
Is that why you put two ms in "lemonade"?
是吗
I did?
好好检查下你的拼写  花瓶
Check your spelling, eye candy.
少来了  你等着看我的厉害吧
Forget that. Wait till you see what else I have.
我会把你挤出这次活动
I'm gonna squeeze you out of business.
就像挤柠檬一样
Like you squeeze a lemon.
-因为做柠檬汁  -成了  我明白
-You know, because to make lemonade... -Yeah, I got it.
这事没完  利奥
This isn't over, Leo.
噢  但我不这么认为
Oh, but I think it is.
他邪恶  他恶毒
He's evil. He's diabolical.
鄙视他
I despise him.
“的”字反着写的确很可爱
The backwards "s" sure is cute though.
好了  她在那呢
Okay, there she is.
噢  我心里没底啊  泰迪
Oh, I don't know about this, Teddy.
-我高攀不起艾丽西娅啊  -什么
-Alicia might be too hot for me. -Wh...
你高攀不起的是我
<i>I'm</i> too hot for you.
没错  但我手里有你的把柄
Yeah, but I got something on you.
好了  这是你的计划
Okay, so here's what you're gonna do.
你走过去  然后说“我是艾米特
You walk over to alicia and you say, "I'm Emmett.
我看见你在这里  想和你打声招呼”
I've seen you around and I just wanted to say hi."
-然后呢  -然后就走开
-Then what? -Then you just walk away.
噢  好的  那你喜欢哪种离开的方式
Oh, okay. What kind of walk are you looking for?
太空步还是机械舞还是滑步
Like a moonwalk or like a robot or like a shuffle...
噢  算了  算了  都不喜欢
Oh, none none... none of the above.
老老实实的走  营造一种神秘感
You just leave. You're creating mystery.
-噢  还有一件事  -住手  你在干嘛
-Oh, one more thing. -Wait, what are you doing?
我需要眼镜  和我的帽子很配
I need those and they go with my hat.
说得好
Good point.
好了  拿下她  老虎
Okay, go get her, tiger.
嗨  我是艾米特
Hi, I'm Emmett.
我看见你在这里  想和你打声招呼
I've seen you around and I wanted to say hi.
可以啊  嗨
Well, hi.
好了  好了
Okay. Okay.
-看来你真需要眼镜  -没错
-So maybe you do need these. -Yeah.
耶
Yeah!
太给力了
That was awesome!
欢迎加入体验乐队
Welcome to the experience.
里奇叔  我喜欢你那动作
Richie dude, I love that move.
就是在架子鼓独奏  你站在中间那段
Where you, like, stood up in the middle of your drum solo.
我的屁股抬不起来了
My butt fell asleep.
给力不  嘿  不如这样
Isn't it great? Hey, you know what?
录完专辑  干脆去现场表演吧
After we record the album, we should play some gigs.
噢  我正有此意  PJ你来吗
Oh, I second that emotion. P.J., are you in?
那还用说
Hecks to the yeah.
好了  大家
All right, gentlemen,
时间不早  节目刚好
Time to take a break for the sake, a pause for the cause.
-同样的结束语  -同样的膀胱
-Same patter. -Same bladder.
天啊  再次见到老爸这么开心  真好
Man, it's awesome to see my dad so happy again.
是啊  他会很享受在厕所里的时光的
Yeah, he enjoys his bathroom.
-我指的是音乐  -噢
-I mean the music, man. -Oh.
为什么你们解散了
Why did you guys ever break up?
这个
Well...
鲍比和一个无所事事的
Bobby was dating this chick
小妞约会
who was always hanging around,
还想把她弄到乐队里
Trying to weasel her way into the band.
-噢  -她快把我和马蒂逼疯了
-Oh. -She drove me and Marty nuts.
-真是噩梦啊  -没错
-Ugh, sounds like a nightmare. -She was.
她叫什么来着
Now what was her name?
-里奇  -艾米
-Richie! -Amy!
就是她
It was Amy.
我听说里奇莅临寒舍了
I heard Richie was in da house.
说到寒舍
Speaking of house,
你还住在你父母的地下室里吗
are you still living in your parents' basement?
当然了
Of course.
搬动一个水床可不是件容易的事情
You know how hard it is to move a waterbed?
-是啊  -嘿  亲爱的
-Yeah. -Hey, honey!
嗨  摇滚明星
Hi, rock star.
你不会相信的
You're not gonna believe this.
-我们准备到外面表演去  -太给力了
-We're gonna start playing gigs again. -That is so rad!
嘿  嘿  嘿  表演“落基山的小妞”
Hey hey hey, play "rocky mountain chick."
-PJ  这歌是关于我的  -给力
-P.J., that's about me. -Rad!
-这个词用对了嘛  -差不多吧
-Did I use that right? -Kind of.
准备  一  二  三  四
Ready? One, two, three, four!
落基山的小妞  你让我为你舞动
Rocky mountain chick, you make my body tick
当你离开时  我就丢了魂  丢了魂
when you're not here, I'm sick sick sick... .
大家  大家  大家  听着  听着
Guys, guys. Guys, guys, guys, guys, guys.
嘿  大水床  感觉不对
Hey, waterbed, it stays on the wrong streets
同志们  加点速度
Guys, pick up the pace.
好好享受下
Have some fun with it.
专辑里就是这么演奏的
This is how we played it on the album.
是吗  那销量如何啊
Yeah, and how did that sell?
听着  跟住我的节奏  明白吗
Look, just follow me, people.
一  二  三  四
A-one, two, three, four.
落基山的小妞  你让我为你舞动
Rocky mountain chick, you make my body tick
当你离开时  我就丢了魂  丢了魂
when you're not here, I'm sick sick sick...
你的金发蓬松凌乱
your blonde disheveled locks
让我神魂颠倒
thrill me to my socks
所有的书呆子和运动员都认为你是个冰美人
all the nerds and jocks think you're a stone-cold fox
冰美人  冰美人
I'm foxy foxy
冰美人  冰美人  冰美人  冰美人
foxy foxy foxy foxy foxy
冰美人  冰美人
foxy foxy
冰美人  冰美人  同志们  配合下
foxy foxy foxy...  guys, hang with me.
嘿  不如休息下吧
Hey, why don't we take a break?
噢  好主意
Ooh, that's a great idea.
我趁机去拿手鼓
It'll give me a chance to grab my tambourine.
-乐队会议  -怎么了  什么事
-Band meeting. -Why? What's up?
什么事  要重蹈1988年的覆辙了
What's up? It's 1988 all over again.
-放松  不会的  -她又开始掌控大权了
-No, it's not. -She's totally taking over.
-我能插句嘴吗  -闭嘴  马蒂
-Can I say something? -Shut up, Marty.
抱歉  应激反应了
Sorry. Force of habit.
那小妞又想混进乐队了
That chick is trying to force her way into the band.
鲍比  你要采取行动了
Bobby, you gotta do something.
好的  说的没错  没错
All right, you're right. You're right.
好了  听着  作为鲍伯·邓肯体验乐队的主心骨
Okay, look, as leader of the Bob Duncan experience,
我会负责的
I'm gonna take charge.
PJ  把你老妈踢出乐队
P.J., go kick your mother out of the band.
欢迎来到利奥三重唱俱乐部
Welcome to club triple-leo, everybody.
我是李离利  凹嗷奥
I'm l to the e to the eh-eh-o!
呦  我叫利奥  我来向大家宣布
yo, my name is Leo and I'm here to tell
我有些茶点  向你们出售
I got some refreshments I'd like to sell
我这里有最好的柠檬  知道吗
I take the best lemons, don't you know?
我将它榨成汁  再加些糖  呦  呦  呦
I just squeeze and add sugar, yo yo yo yo yo
耶  利奥  利奥
yeah, Leo, Leo
耶  利奥
yeah, Leo! .
告诉大家  利奥柠檬汁这里全场免费
Remember, peeps, everything's free at Leo's lemonade,
有爆米花和无线网
Popcorn and wi-fi.
呜
Whoohoo!
如果都免费  你还怎么挣钱
If everything's free, how are you making money?
我不关心挣不挣钱
This isn't about making money.
我只在乎能不能把你打垮  老兄
It's about taking you down, my brotha.
今天我们试试新花样
Now today we're gonna try something a little new.
随便你折腾  不管成败  都有舞伴
Try whatever you want. Either way I have a date.
成了  成了  你就老实的站在这里
Yeah yeah, why don't you just stand here.
等我给你发暗号
And wait until I give you a signal?
嗨  艾丽西娅  听说你是新来的
Hi, Alicia. I know you're new here.
-我叫泰迪  -嗨
-I'm Teddy. -Hi.
你来的时机不太好
So you came here kind of in an awkward time,
正好赶上返校舞会
What with homecoming dance just days away and...
亲娘啊  亲娘啊
Oh my gosh. Oh my gosh.
-亲娘啊  亲娘啊  -怎么了
-Oh my gosh! Oh my gosh! -What?
你看  你看  看到那边的帅哥了吗
Okay okay, so you see that really cute guy there?
哪呢  戴着眼镜和帽子的那个人的后面吗
Where? Behind the guy with the hat and the glasses?
不  不  不  不  不
No no no. No no no.
帽子底下  眼镜后面的那个
Under the hat, behind the glasses.
那个打碎盘子的么
The plate crasher?
他叫艾米特
His name is Emmett.
噢  艾米特  名字都这么迷人
Oh, Emmett... even his name is dreamy.
学校的女生都想和他去返校舞会
Every girl in school wants to go to homecoming with him,
特别是我
especially me.
难道你也是新来的吗
Were you here yesterday?
哦天啊  他来了
Oh my gosh, here he comes.
-嗨  -嗨  泰迪
-Hi. -Hi, Teddy.
噢  他居然知道我的名字
Oh, he knows my name!
嗨  艾米特
Hi, Emmett.
你是想去参加舞会吗
So, uh, are you going to the dance?
其实  我正是想来邀请艾丽西娅的
Actually, that's what I came to talk to Alicia about.
噢  是艾丽西娅啊  当然了  新来的
Oh, Alicia. Of course, the new girl.
你太幸运了
You're so lucky.
好吧
Oh well.
你伤害了我  我会一笑而过
It hurts, but I'll smile through the pain.
我马上闪人  让你俩好好聊聊
Now I'll leave you two alone to talk about.
那美妙的一晚  我会
Your magical evening together while I go nurse my...
哇
Whoa!
别走啊  艾丽西娅
What? No, Alicia...
何必这么费劲呢
Why fight it?
咱俩注定在一起
We're perfect for each other.
落基山的小妞  你让我为你舞动
Rocky mountain chick, you make my heart go tick
当你离开时  我就丢了魂  丢了魂
when you're not here, I'm sick sick sick.
-嘿  老妈  -嘿  我的首席吉他手
-Hey, mom. -Hey there, my lead guitarist.
好了  好了  关于这事  我想和你谈谈
Yeah yeah, about that... can I... can I talk to you?
好啊  什么事
Sure. What about?
其实  我认为如果从查莉
Actually I think it would be better if you...
的嘴里说出来比较好
If you heard it from Charlie.
说吧  查莉  告诉妈咪你的想法
Go ahead, Charlie. Tell mommy what's on your mind.
妈咪
Mommy...
你看  把她气得连话都说不出来了
Okay, she's obviously too upset to say anything.
不会吧  你不高兴了  为什么啊
No no no. You're upset? Why?
呃  她认为你加入到乐队中不是个好主意
Um, she thinks it's a bad idea for you to be in the band.
-查莉说的这话  -是的
-Charlie said that? -Yes.
-你说的吗  查莉  -不是  妈咪
-Did you say that, Charlie? -No, mommy.
等一下  PJ  你不想让我进乐队
Wait, P.J., you don't want me in the band?
但是我会给乐队增色不少
But it's so much better with me in it.
是啊  是啊  但问题是
Yeah yeah, it is, but the problem is...
-这就是问题  -是什么
-That is the problem. -What is?
你太抢眼了  太抢眼了  太抢眼了
You're good. You're too good. You're too good.
我们都知道你是大明星
And we all know you're a star.
但当你站在老爸旁边时
But when you're next to dad...
-他就会黯然失色  -没错
-He fades into the woodwork. -Ex... yes!
你想想看  鲍勃·邓肯体验乐队
I mean, come on. The Bob Duncan experience?
-变成了  艾米·邓肯体验乐队  -正解
-Hello? The Amy Duncan experience? -Exactly!
-噢  -没错
-Oh! -Exactly.
我不能这么对他
I can't do that to him.
我能吗
Can I?
不  不
No no,
因为你是个好人
Because you are too good a person.
-可恶的人性  -是啊  是啊
-Darn my humanity. -Yeah yeah.
好了  好了
Okay okay.
可算说出口了
Pulled that out.
不过  你在压力之下总掉链子
By the way, you are terrible under pressure.
对不起
Sorry.
耶
Yeah!
拉拉队表演还未结束
Those cheerleaders aren't done yet.
他们会帮您的柠檬汁续杯
They'll now be serving your next round of lemonade!
-呜  -耶
-Whoo! -<i>Yeah!</i>
盖比娱乐嘉年华精彩继续
The entertainment marathon continues here at Gabe's.
向大家介绍一支新晋乐队
With a hot new group:
鲍勃·邓肯体验乐队
The Bob Duncan experience.
-耶  -耶
-Yeah! -Yeah!
嘿  别给我丢脸
Hey, don't disappoint me.
嘿
Hey.
你去预订下音乐
Now that you're booking live music,
我给自己加了一点儿戏份儿
You know, I'm putting a little something together myself.
所以我先跟你串通好了
So we should talk.
好了  乡亲父老们  下午好
All right. Good afternoon, Edward drive!
我们是鲍勃·邓肯体验乐队
We are the Bob Duncan experience.
我想把这第一首歌献给
And I would like to dedicate this very first song.
我的落基山小妞
To my very own Rocky mountain chick.
就是我  大家好  我就是落基山小妞  呜
That's me, everybody. I'm the Rocky mountain chick, Whoo!
落基山的小妞  你让我为你舞动
Rocky mountain chick, you make my heart go tick
当你离开时  我就丢了魂  丢了魂
when you're not here, I'm sick sick sick... .
哇  拉拉队  现场演出  客人满座
Wow... cheerleaders, live music, a full house?
你赢了  盖比
You win, Gabe.
柠檬汁战役结束了
The great lemonade war is over.
我哪里赢了
What did I win?
-我赔了两百多块  -我赔了三百块
-I'm down more than $200. -I'm down $300.
租移动厕所可不便宜啊
Renting porta-potties is expensive.
怎么弥补呢
How are we gonna make this up?
嘿  我邻居家有鳄梨树
Hey, my next door neighbor has an avocado tree.
可以开个鳄梨酱店
We'll start a guacamole stand.
利奥和盖比鳄梨酱店
Leo and Gabe's guacamole stand.
盖比和利奥鳄梨酱店
Gabe and Leo's guacamole stand.
好了  查莉  这周我从盖比那里学了一课
Well, Charlie, I learned a lesson from Gabe this week:
当生活不如意时
When life hands you lemons,
就和艾米特去返校舞会
You go to homecoming with Emmett.
知道吗  事实就是
You know, but the truth is.
我们有可能玩得很开心
We're probably gonna have a good time.
-只不过是跳一支舞  -是毕业舞会前
-And it's just one dance. -Until prom.
等等  你说什么  你到底有我多少把柄
Wait, what? What do you have on me?
-噢  不是很多  -噢
-Oh, not much. -Oh!
“泰迪答应去毕业舞会”
"Teddy says yes to prom."
“泰迪答应结婚”
"Teddy says yes to marriage"?
那个动了点手脚
That one took a bit of editing.
如果他认为这些都有戏
If he thinks that's gonna happen,
那他需要些运气了  查莉
He's gonna need some good luck, Charlie.
盖比和利奥鳄梨酱店
Gabe and Leo's guacamole stand.
利奥和盖比鳄梨酱店
Leo and Gabe's guacamole stand.
-盖比和利奥  -利奥和盖比
-Gabe and Leo's. -Leo and Gabe's.
-<i>Gabe and Leo's.</i> <i>-</i> <i>Leo and Gabe's.</i>
-盖比和利奥  -利奥和盖比
-好了  好了  我同意了  -好吧
-You know what? Fine. -Fine.
-随便了  -随便了
-Whatever! -Whatever?
你就不能在死之前化解此事吗
You can't have said that before we were dead?